Boston Dispensary Records MS214
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Employment records, 1920 -- 1967; MS214.007; 6.0 Linear Feet
  Employee address cards and committee affiliations are arranged alphabetically by last name, but are not item level cataloged. Employee cards includes the employees name; address; the department they worked for; and the dates and titles of positions they held. Committee affiliation cards list the members various committees.
  75 years from the date of creation. Open for research.
  - Employee personnel files, 1920 -- 1967; MS214.007.001
    - Abbott, Florence, 1922; MS214.007.004.00025 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Abruzzzese, Rocchina, 1960; MS214.007.004.00026 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
      75 years from the date of creation.
    - Adams, Josephine, 1933; MS214.007.004.00027 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Adams, Rachel, 1938; MS214.007.004.00028 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Albion, Eugenia, 1941; MS214.007.004.00029 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Alden, Minerva, 1942; MS214.007.004.00030 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Allen, Gwendoline, 1962; MS214.007.004.00031 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Almy, Helen, 1924; MS214.007.004.00032 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Andelman, Ruth, 1937; MS214.007.004.00033 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Anderson, Gerda, 1924; MS214.007.004.00034 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Andren, Thekla, 1941; MS214.007.004.00035 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Antilla, Jayne, 1965; MS214.007.004.00036 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Arico, Josephine, 1931; MS214.007.004.00037 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Armstrong, Carolyn, 1960; MS214.007.004.00038 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Arnao, Jean, 1961; MS214.007.004.00039 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Aronson, Pearl, 1934; MS214.007.004.00040 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Aucoin, Roberta Clark, 1962; MS214.007.004.00041 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bacon, Gladys, 1924; MS214.007.004.00042 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Baker, Dorothy, 1957; MS214.007.004.00043 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Baker, Lorraine, 1957; MS214.007.004.00044 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Balicer, Stella, 1934; MS214.007.004.00045 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Balis, Nancy, 1939; MS214.007.004.00046 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Barber, Edith, 1928; MS214.007.004.00047 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Barden, Elizabeth, 1934; MS214.007.004.00048 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Barron, Richard, 1950; MS214.007.004.00049 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Barus, Deborah, 1941; MS214.007.004.00050 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bassett, Sarah, 1951; MS214.007.004.00051 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bastek, Patricia, 1962; MS214.007.004.00052 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bearse, Emily, 1939; MS214.007.004.00053 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Belair, Valerie, 1941; MS214.007.004.00054 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Beliner, Marilyn, 1950; MS214.007.004.00055 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Belsar, Evelyn, 1931; MS214.007.004.00056 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Benner, Dorothy, 1946; MS214.007.004.00057 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Benyon, Marion, 1946; MS214.007.004.00058 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Berger, Ethel, 1941; MS214.007.004.00059 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bergkuist, Helen, 1942; MS214.007.004.00060 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bering, Jennie, 1962; MS214.007.004.00061 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bigelow, Elizabeth, 1926; MS214.007.004.00062 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bilder, Shirley, 1945; MS214.007.004.00063 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Billings, Cornelia, 1956; MS214.007.004.00064 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bilotta, Rose, 1948; MS214.007.004.00065 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bissell, Emily, 1930; MS214.007.004.00066 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bissonnette, Claire, 1962; MS214.007.004.00067 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Blackadar, Marion, 1934; MS214.007.004.00068 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Blackett, Anne, 1925; MS214.007.004.00069 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Blake, Alice, 1934; MS214.007.004.00070 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Blake, Marjorie, 1941; MS214.007.004.00071 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Blandau, Olive, 1942; MS214.007.004.00072 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bliss, Elizabeth, 1944; MS214.007.004.00073 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Blomquist, Gustave, 1931; MS214.007.004.00074 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Blunt, Brenda, 1933; MS214.007.004.00075 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bolivar, Helen, 1929; MS214.007.004.00076 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Borcherding, Ruth, 1930; MS214.007.004.00077 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bowler, Rebecca, 1955; MS214.007.004.00078 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bowman, Maude, 1926; MS214.007.004.00079 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bradley, Kathleen, 1941; MS214.007.004.00080 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Brady, Helene, 1930; MS214.007.004.00081 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bramhall, Priscilla, 1940; MS214.007.004.00082 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Brass, Harry, 1950; MS214.007.004.00083 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Brennan, Joan, 1929; MS214.007.004.00084 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Brewster, Dorothy, 1929; MS214.007.004.00085 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Briggs, Adelaide, 1939; MS214.007.004.00086 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Brooke, Marie, 1939; MS214.007.004.00087 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Brooks, Betty, 1961; MS214.007.004.00088 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Brooks, Rachel, 1940; MS214.007.004.00089 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bruce, Bessie, 1931; MS214.007.004.00090 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Bruno, Jeannette, 1963; MS214.007.004.00091 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Buchanan, Gwendolyn, 1963; MS214.007.004.00092 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Buckner, Dorothy, 1930; MS214.007.004.00093 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Burack, Bernice, 1934; MS214.007.004.00094 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Burgess, Mary, 1927; MS214.007.004.00095 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Burkhardt, Grace, 1929; MS214.007.004.00096 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Burns, Adelaide, 1945; MS214.007.004.00097 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Burns, Mary, 1950; MS214.007.004.00098 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Burris, Evadine, 1935; MS214.007.004.00099 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Calder, Mildred, 1943; MS214.007.004.00100 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Callahan, Mary G., 1929; MS214.007.004.00101 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Callahan, Mary L., 1932; MS214.007.004.00102 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Callahan, Rita, 1962; MS214.007.004.00103 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Calver, Elinor, 1935; MS214.007.004.00104 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Campion, Mary, 1966; MS214.007.004.00105 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Canterbury, Edith, 1925; MS214.007.004.00106 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Carbone, Eileen, 1959; MS214.007.004.00107 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Carbone, Florina, 1940; MS214.007.004.00108 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Carlisle-Worker, Elizabeth, 1939; MS214.007.004.00109 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Carnes, Otis, 1935; MS214.007.004.00110 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Carpenter, Roberta, 1945; MS214.007.004.00111 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Caruso, Evelyn, 1956; MS214.007.004.00112 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Casey, Agnes, 1928; MS214.007.004.00113 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cassanos, Helen, 1955; MS214.007.004.00114 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Castles, Thomas, 1964; MS214.007.004.00115 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Ceder, Miriam, 1929; MS214.007.004.00116 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Chace, Mary, 1926; MS214.007.004.00117 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Chambers, Frances, 1958; MS214.007.004.00118 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Chandler, Marjorie-Jane, 1924; MS214.007.004.00119 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Chapin, Grace, 1938; MS214.007.004.00120 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Chin, Mildred, 1956; MS214.007.004.00121 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Churchill, Frances, 1929; MS214.007.004.00122 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Ciccone, Julia, 1956; MS214.007.004.00123 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cicero, Carnella, 1955; MS214.007.004.00124 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Clark, Annie, 1926; MS214.007.004.00125 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Clark, Esther, 1962; MS214.007.004.00126 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cleary, Ann, 1961; MS214.007.004.00127 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Coburn, Natalie, 1933; MS214.007.004.00128 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Codman, Margaret, 1941; MS214.007.004.00129 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Colan, Alice, 1957; MS214.007.004.00130 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Colby, Marian, 1946; MS214.007.004.00131 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Comperchio, Vito, 1932; MS214.007.004.00132 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Condon, Agnes, 1963; MS214.007.004.00133 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cone, Grace, 1931; MS214.007.004.00134 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Connell, Helen, 1921; MS214.007.004.00135 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Conners, Alice, 1940; MS214.007.004.00136 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Coolen, Josephine, 1930; MS214.007.004.00137 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cooney, Josephine, 1924; MS214.007.004.00138 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cooper, Beatrice, 1934; MS214.007.004.00139 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Corey, Beverly, 1963; MS214.007.004.00140 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cotter, Dorothy, 1947; MS214.007.004.00141 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cotter, Lesley, 1947; MS214.007.004.00142 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Couphlin, Helen, 1928; MS214.007.004.00143 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Crean, Ellen, 1936; MS214.007.004.00144 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Criado, MaRosa, 1961; MS214.007.004.00145 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cropper, Sylvia, 1961; MS214.007.004.00146 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cross, Bernice, 1932; MS214.007.004.00147 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Crowder, Alice, 1948; MS214.007.004.00148 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cubiles, Ricardo, 1956; MS214.007.004.00149 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Culbert, Eleanor, 1937; MS214.007.004.00150 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cullen, Dorris, 1953; MS214.007.004.00151 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cullinane, Marie, 1957; MS214.007.004.00152 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cummings, Mary, 1929; MS214.007.004.00153 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Cunningham, Gertrude, 1955; MS214.007.004.00154 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Curtis, Violet, 1941; MS214.007.004.00155 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Daley, Kathleen, 1939; MS214.007.004.00156 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Danielian, Leo, 1929; MS214.007.004.00157 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Danielian, Virginia, 1929; MS214.007.004.00158 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Davis, Catherine, 1950; MS214.007.004.00159 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Davis, Ruth, 1929; MS214.007.004.00160 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Davis, Selma, 1934; MS214.007.004.00161 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Day, Ruth, 1963; MS214.007.004.00162 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Defren, Lorraine, 1926; MS214.007.004.00163 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dennis, Esther, 1947; MS214.007.004.00164 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Derfel, Ann, 1933; MS214.007.004.00165 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Devney, Minnie, 1946; MS214.007.004.00166 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - di Cicco, Filomena, 1958; MS214.007.004.00167 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Diaz, Bernadette, 1963; MS214.007.004.00168 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dill, Florence, 1938; MS214.007.004.00169 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Doherty, Alice, 1928; MS214.007.004.00170 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dolan, Louise, 1943; MS214.007.004.00171 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dolan, Mary, 1938; MS214.007.004.00172 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Donahue, Marion, 1958; MS214.007.004.00173 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Donald, Jean, 1930; MS214.007.004.00174 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Donovan, Margaret, 1945; MS214.007.004.00175 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Donovan, Marie, 1927; MS214.007.004.00176 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dooley, Margaret, 1945; MS214.007.004.00177 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Doucet, Estelle, 1960; MS214.007.004.00178 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Douglas, George, 1959; MS214.007.004.00179 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dragone, Emma, 1930; MS214.007.004.00180 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Driscoll, Catherine, 1927; MS214.007.004.00181 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Drysgula, Stella, 1957; MS214.007.004.00182 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dudley, James, 1933; MS214.007.004.00183 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dunks, Abbie, 1946; MS214.007.004.00184 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dunn, Esther, 1921; MS214.007.004.00185 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dunn, Vivian, 1938; MS214.007.004.00186 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dunning, Rebecca, 1925; MS214.007.004.00187 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dunphy, Nancy, 1936; MS214.007.004.00188 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dupriez, Marie Louise, 1942; MS214.007.004.00189 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Dylie, Ellen, 1952; MS214.007.004.00190 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Eads, Johanna, 1961; MS214.007.004.00191 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Earl, Aileen, 1948; MS214.007.004.00192 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Edwards, Beatrice, 1948; MS214.007.004.00193 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Edwards, Elizabeth, 1955; MS214.007.004.00194 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Eisenberg, Carol, 1965; MS214.007.004.00195 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Emerson, Olga, 1954; MS214.007.004.00196 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Engstrand, Lillian, 1924; MS214.007.004.00197 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Erikson, Mary Ann, 1959; MS214.007.004.00198 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Estabrook, Anna, 1937; MS214.007.004.00199 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Estabrook, Helen, 1926; MS214.007.004.00200 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Fanning, Melvin, 1932; MS214.007.004.00201 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Faucett, Emily, 1939; MS214.007.004.00202 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Fedrini, Helena, 1945; MS214.007.004.00203 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Feild, Helen, 1927; MS214.007.004.00204 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Felch, Jane, 1929; MS214.007.004.00205 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Felker, Mildred, 1931; MS214.007.004.00206 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Fernald, Rosamond, 1928; MS214.007.004.00207 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Finer, Pauline, 1934; MS214.007.004.00208 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Finn, Mary, 1936; MS214.007.004.00209 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Finnegan, Caroline, 1926; MS214.007.004.00210 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Finnegan, Mary, 1954; MS214.007.004.00211 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Fitzgerald, Maurice, 1953; MS214.007.004.00212 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Fitzpatrick, Mary, 1946; MS214.007.004.00213 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Flynn, Mary, 1965; MS214.007.004.00214 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Folger, Alice, 1958; MS214.007.004.00215 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Forbes, Bessie Mae, 1937; MS214.007.004.00216 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Forbes, Clare, 1946; MS214.007.004.00217 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Foss, Jennifer, 1942; MS214.007.004.00218 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Freeman, James, 1933; MS214.007.004.00219 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Frissell, Alice, 1931; MS214.007.004.00220 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Frizzell, Jean, 1941; MS214.007.004.00221 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Fronte, Theresa, 1940; MS214.007.004.00222 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Furst, Helen, 1940; MS214.007.004.00223 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Fyhr, Evelyn, 1947; MS214.007.004.00224 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gale, Marion, 1943; MS214.007.004.00225 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gallagher, Emily, 1935; MS214.007.004.00226 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gammans, Katherine, 1932; MS214.007.004.00227 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gardner, Willetta, 1949; MS214.007.004.00228 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gaston, Mary, 1927; MS214.007.004.00229 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gearty, Elizabeth, 1963; MS214.007.004.00230 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Genthner, Marion, 1931; MS214.007.004.00231 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gerald, Nina, 1929; MS214.007.004.00232 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gerig, Mary, 1923; MS214.007.004.00233 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gerstein, Evelyn, 1935; MS214.007.004.00234 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gheradi, Anita, 1957; MS214.007.004.00235 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gibson, Pearl, 1945; MS214.007.004.00236 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gillis, Mary, 1943; MS214.007.004.00237 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gillman, Elizabeth, 1939; MS214.007.004.00238 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gioshes, Shirley, 1961; MS214.007.004.00239 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Girard, Kenneth, 1958; MS214.007.004.00240 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Glick, Gertrude, 1942; MS214.007.004.00241 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Goldberg, Florence, 1939; MS214.007.004.00242 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Goldberg, Ruth, 1930; MS214.007.004.00243 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Goldstein, Mindel, 1950; MS214.007.004.00244 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Goodman, Geneva, 1963; MS214.007.004.00245 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gorham, Marion, 1955; MS214.007.004.00246 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gough, Ann, 1963; MS214.007.004.00247 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gould, Hazel, 1953; MS214.007.004.00248 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gracetta, Elizabeth, 1963; MS214.007.004.00249 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Graham, Ruth, 1924; MS214.007.004.00250 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Grant, Julia, 1950; MS214.007.004.00251 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gray, Mary, 1943; MS214.007.004.00252 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Grealis, Katherine, 1965; MS214.007.004.00253 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Greeley, Faith, 1955; MS214.007.004.00254 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Green, Mary, 1955; MS214.007.004.00255 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Greenbaum Lwell, 1952; MS214.007.004.00256 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Grundy, Elizabeth, 1936; MS214.007.004.00257 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Guarino, Gloria, 1950; MS214.007.004.00258 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Guillet, Marie, 1946; MS214.007.004.00259 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Gunning, Rose, 1941; MS214.007.004.00260 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hacker, Dorothy, 1929; MS214.007.004.00261 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Haehnel, Margaret, 1946; MS214.007.004.00262 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Haliburton, Eva, 1948; MS214.007.004.00263 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hall, Priscilla, 1946; MS214.007.004.00264 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Halpern, Gertrude, 1933; MS214.007.004.00265 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hamberg, Valborg, 1956; MS214.007.004.00266 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hamilton, Margaret, 1955; MS214.007.004.00267 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hamilton, Marie, 1937; MS214.007.004.00268 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hanigan, Anna, 1946; MS214.007.004.00269 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hanlon, Nancy, 1955; MS214.007.004.00270 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hansbury, Elizabeth, 1933; MS214.007.004.00271 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hansen, Jennifer, 1931; MS214.007.004.00272 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Harbeson, Ida, 1944; MS214.007.004.00273 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Harding, Harriette, 1930; MS214.007.004.00274 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hardley, Anne, 1939; MS214.007.004.00275 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hardy, Arthur, 1927; MS214.007.004.00276 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Harrington, Catherine, 1959; MS214.007.004.00277 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Harris, Catherine, 1927; MS214.007.004.00278 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hawko, Elizabeth, 1944; MS214.007.004.00279 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hayden, Catina, 1959; MS214.007.004.00280 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hayward, Eleanor, 1939; MS214.007.004.00281 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hazard, Mary, 1945; MS214.007.004.00282 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hazen, Catherine, 1934; MS214.007.004.00283 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hazlett, Lexie, 1959; MS214.007.004.00284 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Heald, Paula, 1926; MS214.007.004.00285 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Heard, Beatrice, 1962; MS214.007.004.00286 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hearsey, Mildred, 1924; MS214.007.004.00287 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Heath, Katherine, 1956; MS214.007.004.00288 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hecht, Frances, 1934; MS214.007.004.00289 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hellmer, Alice, 1932; MS214.007.004.00290 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Henes, Catherine, 1939; MS214.007.004.00291 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hershman, Bessie, 1942; MS214.007.004.00292 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hewitt, Barbara, 1940; MS214.007.004.00293 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hilferding, Rose, 1948; MS214.007.004.00294 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hill, Carolyn, 1928; MS214.007.004.00295 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hill, Wendy, 1957; MS214.007.004.00296 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hite, Dorothy, 1929; MS214.007.004.00297 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hodge, Margaret, 1938; MS214.007.004.00298 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Holmes, Ruth, 1949; MS214.007.004.00299 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Holmgren, Agda, 1950; MS214.007.004.00300 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hooker, Helen, 1944; MS214.007.004.00301 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hope, Alice, 1929; MS214.007.004.00302 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Horvarth, Marjorie, 1922; MS214.007.004.00303 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Horvitz, Beatrice, 1929; MS214.007.004.00304 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Houck, Margaret, 1957; MS214.007.004.00305 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Houghton, Florence, 1932; MS214.007.004.00306 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Howe, Katherine, 1929; MS214.007.004.00307 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hughes, Florence, 1929; MS214.007.004.00308 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hunt, Bessie, 1925; MS214.007.004.00309 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hurst, Dorothy, 1945; MS214.007.004.00310 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hurst, Eva, 1951; MS214.007.004.00311 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hurtado, Dolores, 1949; MS214.007.004.00312 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Huston, Corinne, 1960; MS214.007.004.00313 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hutcheson, Mary, 1946; MS214.007.004.00314 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Hyatt, Gilbert, 1926; MS214.007.004.00315 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Iannuzzi, Mary, 1947; MS214.007.004.00316 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Irwin, Lovicy, 1929; MS214.007.004.00317 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Jackson, Ruth, 1937; MS214.007.004.00318 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Jacobson, Ruby, 1928; MS214.007.004.00319 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - James, Freda, 1925; MS214.007.004.00320 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Janeway, Elizabeth, 1934; MS214.007.004.00321 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Jodice, Muriel, 1961; MS214.007.004.00322 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Johnson, Mabel, 1922; MS214.007.004.00323 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Johnson, Mary, 1938; MS214.007.004.00324 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Johnston, Florence, 1928; MS214.007.004.00325 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Jones, Elma, 1937; MS214.007.004.00326 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Jones, Harriet, 1932; MS214.007.004.00327 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Jones, Myrtle, 1958; MS214.007.004.00328 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Joy, Elizabeth, 1930; MS214.007.004.00329 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Juergens, Marion, 1934; MS214.007.004.00330 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Jurgelewicz, Evelyn, 1949; MS214.007.004.00331 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kaelin, Florence, 1922; MS214.007.004.00332 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kaufman, Martha, 1928; MS214.007.004.00333 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Keating, Ellen, 1961; MS214.007.004.00334 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Keeffe, Elsie, 1948; MS214.007.004.00335 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kelley, Anna, 1958; MS214.007.004.00336 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kelley, Katherine, 1932; MS214.007.004.00337 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kelly, Rose, 1954; MS214.007.004.00338 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kennedy, Doris, 1941; MS214.007.004.00339 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kenny, Elizabeth, 1925; MS214.007.004.00340 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kenton, Adeline, 1944; MS214.007.004.00341 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kerr, Florence, 1931; MS214.007.004.00342 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kerryon, Esther, 1938; MS214.007.004.00343 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Key, Edna, 1931; MS214.007.004.00344 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kilpatrick, Marilyn, 1959; MS214.007.004.00345 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kimball, Louise, 1950; MS214.007.004.00346 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - King, Mary, 1953; MS214.007.004.00347 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kirkendall, Stella, 1938; MS214.007.004.00348 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kittredge, Pauline, 1923; MS214.007.004.00349 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Klim, Charles, 1959; MS214.007.004.00350 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kline, Harold, 1924; MS214.007.004.00351 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kondej, Mildred, 1934; MS214.007.004.00352 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kruse, Ilse, 1946; MS214.007.004.00353 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Kurland, Sally, 1926; MS214.007.004.00354 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Lafricain, Ruth, 1929; MS214.007.004.00355 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Lambeck, Ebba, 1964; MS214.007.004.00356 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Lambert, Else, 1955; MS214.007.004.00357 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Landstrom, Amy, 1947; MS214.007.004.00358 (Box MS214 Shared 4)
    - Lane, Mary, 1933; MS214.007.004.00359 (Box MS214 Shared 4)